[{"answer": "I was thinking about this.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "What's your next great idea?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes, we do.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "Do you know any of the other homeowners whose houses have been affected, Jude?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "One of them at least was that we talked to, because he's the one that came around after the fireman to tell us if they were having to check all of the water lines.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Are they all showing the same kind of stiff upper lip spirit that you are?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Right now, not much.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What are the -- what are the experts telling you?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Are you going to stay there, Richard?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Are you concerned about that?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Those are your words.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "That's an unbelievable analogy to make, isn't it?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I'm going to try again.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Why is it uncanny other than they're two young black boys?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "But you go on to say liberal media should ask if what these two black teens did to a woman and baby is the reason people think blacks might be risky.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Of him flicking the bird?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "But you know why they're angry?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "They indict him with photographs of Trayvon Martin that don't accurately portray the person.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Are you going to carry on tweeting?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I -- of course I do.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "But do you accept that what you've done is not helpful to George?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I don't think it makes any sense to take a guy who's number one in the time slot, even though all the TV critics, the New York wise guys think that he's not hip and he's not cool, we went through this with Conan.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Do you think he'll be out in a year's time?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I think it was -- it doesn't really matter if it was fair.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Was it fair, though?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "If money is right, everyone is available, Howard.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Are you available if they decided to go in a different direction?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, I think they have to get over this period of media attention.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How do you fix it?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "I think bad management -- change of management.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Bad management?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "But one reason it gave me pause is that I was able to report a couple of weeks ago on \"The Daily Beast\" that Matt Lauer had offered to step aside.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What does that tell you about what is really going on there?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "We are increasingly living in a garrison state.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Three a month?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Well, you know, pretty harsh words about him being mean to children.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "It's a pointless point-scoring exercise, isn't it?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "The solution is this, the American people would, I'm sure, be quite happy to pay five dollars each to go and see the White House.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "You know, there's a lot of people like myself that support civil unions.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "Ben Ferguson, will you always remember where you were when Bill O'Reilly publicly supported gay rights in this extraordinary manner?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "But also are very clear.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "Ben, are you married?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "You're married.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Let Abby Hunstman?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "Because I believe that marriage -- and the sanctity of marriage, and what it represents, was important for me and for what I believe in.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Why did you not just get a civil union then?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "Could you imagine a situation in 2016 where the Republican candidate who takes on whoever the Democratic candidate is would be anti same-sex marriage?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "It would be -- I don't think they could actually win a general election, is my answer to that.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 754, "question": "No, what I mean is, could you imagine a Republican candidate who didn't support same-sex marriage in 2016?", "qSentId": 753}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 780, "question": "But this must feel a bit surreal, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 779}, {"answer": "'ALOISIO: So, it was about two years ago, when I was 15.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "When did you have the germ of the idea?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "Fundamentally, I think it came down to the idea.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 801, "question": "What was it about you, do you think, that they liked?", "qSentId": 800}, {"answer": "No, I'm really enthusiastic by the opportunity at Yahoo1.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "Or are you hopeful it's going to become ever bigger?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "No, from my perspective, I think we have robust I.P. that we've been developing for the last two years.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "Reaction?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "You thinking of doing a new campaign, because he's worth it?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "No, I do have a girlfriend.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 825, "question": "Are you single at the moment?", "qSentId": 824}, {"answer": "'ALOISIO: Yes.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "I don't think that really comes into it.", "docId": "130327pmt", "aSentId": 829, "question": "How is she feeling about the fact you're now worth 30 million dollars?", "qSentId": 828}]